Meet ZernoFi — the first RWA aggregator for Ukrainian agribusiness…
Built on Solana. Yield paid in USDC. No token volatility.
The world's farmers face a $160 billion annual financing gap.
Banks take months. Crypto offers no real-asset yield. Both markets are broken.
ZernoFi fixes both with three simple steps.
Deposit USDC into a verified farm pool from just $100.
Crops grow. You earn USDC plus $UAAGRO tokens.
Two live pools with pre-vetted Ukrainian partners.
Premium Wheat at 18.5% APY.
Escargot Farm at 24% APY — EU export grade.
Calculate your returns in seconds.
$10,000 in Wheat equals +$1,850 base yield.
With $UAAGRO boost: +$2,150. A clear 16% bonus.
Every position, every payout, every reward — tracked live.
Portfolio value, $UAAGRO balance, pool progress — all in one dashboard.
$UAAGRO is optional. But it's your edge.
Stake for +3% APY boost. Vote on governance.
Sell on Jupiter anytime — secondary liquidity for an illiquid asset.
This is the bridge between real farms and real DeFi.
Visit www.zernofi.org. Start with $100.